[Music]
Hello, welcome to our special presentation.
I am Vivek Mittal.  Friends, if we
look at the market today, it has been a roller coaster
market and as we saw,
Nifty had opened flat in the beginning.
After that the dip started.  Then there was
recovery from the dip.  But then once again there was a
big dip and Nifty at one point
even reached the range of 25600 and after that
somehow Nifty sustained itself
above 700.  So somewhere we can say that there was
a smart recovery, you can also see it on the chart,
in the last half or 40 minutes from the lower levels, we can say that a great
smart recovery was seen in the market.
But we cannot say
that the market has closed in green today
or we have been able to follow the momentum of a bullish trend which was gained yesterday, so
this momentum was not gained today,
but now how much will this momentum grow further, in
which direction will it go and are there any stock
specific news, let's talk about all of that,
market expert has joined us,
Vibhu Jain ji, Vibhu ji, hi, good afternoon,
thank you so much for joining in, Vibhu ji,
tell me today
sir, the way the market is moving,
if I talk about the last 10 days, then
somewhere or the other we have seen a lot of selling in the market.   The
market started a significant downward journey from its top.
But in today's or yesterday's session, which was
last Friday's session, we have
seen the market recovering a bit.  One, the selling
pressure was seen to be subsiding.  But
still, the way I
see the market, I still
feel that in the coming times, even the
month of February may
not be anything special for our Indian market.  And
the way we are
not seeing any good positive news at the global level right now.
So at this time the market
seems to be moving towards the downside.
How far do you see the downside?
Sir, right now our
Nifty is already running around 25,700.  25,300 is going to be an
important crucial support level.
If the level of 25,300 is broken
then definitely we can see the level of 25,000 also
coming into the market.  So
before that we should not think about the buy side in the market.  One should
not
think about going long in the market right now.  It might be possible that the market has
seen a lot of selling in the last few days.  So let's pause for a while now, let the
market remain range bound for a few days.
Stay in consolidation.  The market remained in this range, moving 100 points upwards or
100-10 points downwards.
But until the market breaks one of your important
resistance levels of 259 to
25900,
we should not think at all about going long in the market
and the way the
market is currently looking consistently downwards,
we may also see levels of 25300 and 25000 in the coming days.
Ok?  So here is the market talk, 25300 and
25900 are two crucial levels and the market
is currently almost in the middle of both those
levels, although 25700 is the
level of 900 which is closer, but until it
crosses 25900, there will not be fresh momentum in the market,
but momentum is
largely due to news and today there was momentum in Eternal's stock,
one thing that was
going on since today's morning session was that there was
talk of increasing the weightage of the company in MSCI and their share holding
pattern actually
indicated to some extent that the
headroom of FI in it is visible in the future,
this was a positive news for KFI Holding,
due to which there was
good news in today's morning session in Turnal, there was good
momentum, but after that the stock lost momentum
and why did it lose it because
a statement came from the Labor Ministry that all these
quick commerce companies, be it
zmato, sg blanket and zpto
Companies like these will have to stop
delivering goods within the 10-minute time limit
because their employees were
a little upset due to this and due to this,
a non-safety issue was also seen on the roads.
Vibhu ji, please tell me
your opinion on the shares like Internal and Swiggy which are listed on the market.
Sir, if I
look at the stock technically in the internal sector, then somewhere or the other, I
see an up trend in the stock.  If you keep your view
on this stock for about a year, then
definitely from here I see a
very good positive in the stock,
which is that this stock is going towards the top of the market.
If you need confirmation that we have to
enter above this level, then
₹305 is an important resistance level.
If this stock
breaks the level of ₹305 in the coming days within one to two weeks, then
we should definitely make an entry in this stock
and after that, the first resistance for us will be
around ₹350 where we can book our profit.
If Eternal
stock breaks that resistance level well and
is able to sustain there, then definitely we
can see an even bigger rally in it.  The
way the government order has come that Yes's
Swigg, Zomato or Quick,
which is a service providing company,
delivers your home within 10 minutes.
Somewhere there was a big issue
with his employees that his
working hours became very intense.
He was feeling a lot of work pressure in that.
So somewhere this is a positive
step of the government towards the labour.
But if we look at it from the company's perspective, then
somewhere or the other
we can see its impact on their efficiency and their product delivery.
But technically, the
stock looks quite good.  One can think about making an entry in this
and I would also like to give a strict stop loss in the
stock which will be
around 275, if the stock
breaks the level of 275 then we should
definitely take exit from the stock but
technically the stock is looking quite bullish at this time.   That's
right.  So now you have got the opinion in Eternal
and now
Jain sir has told you how to make the strategy.  Let's move ahead.  The
next stock is Bank of
Maharashtra.  Vibhu ji, the results came here today
and the results were quite amazing to see.
Again Bank of Maharashtra
started the results season on a
good note for banking stocks and PSU stocks too
seemed to be basking in the cheer.
Looking at the net profit of the company, the bank has
increased by about 26.5%.  Operating profit increased by 18% and net
interest income increased by about 16%.  Net
NPA, which is essential to reduce, has reduced further. It has
reduced from 118% to 15% and gross NPA has
also reduced from 1.72% to 1.6%.
Banking stocks had a good start.
How are you seeing the results?  Bank of
Maharashtra and all the PSU banks?
Vivek ji, if I talk specifically about Bank
of Maharashtra, then I have already
recommended Bank of Maharashtra many times on Money.
I have
talked about this stock many times that Yes is a
very good bank.  The performance of this bank
seems to be improving every time.  Even we have already suggested
this stock to our clients at much lower
levels.
We have talked about this stock continuously.
Bank of Maharashtra
is one of my favorite banks, especially among PSU banks.
Its technical chart also looks even more
bullish to me from here
and I think that
in the coming time we may
see even more rise in this stock from here.
An important resistance is going to be
around 7273,
sorry.  If the stock breaks the ₹72 level around ₹7273
and sustains above it
for a week or two,
then we will definitely see a fresh rally in this stock.
But if you ask me that
within the banking banks like our PNB
or other PSU banks, among them Bank of
Maharashtra seems to me to be one such bank
which is a consistent performer and whose
valuation has not yet got the value unlocking
that it should have got.
So I am fully hopeful
that in the times to come,
Bank of Maharashtra can be a big
game changer among PSU banks and
we will definitely see its valuation unlocking.
But for this you will need to
hold this stock for a long time.
Ok.  Another result that came during the
market was that of ICICI Piden.  In this, the
profit of the company jumped by 19% and
if you look at the net premium income here, it was
down by about 4% but the
solvency ratio of the bank has improved.   The
persistency ratio is almost stable.
And if you see, the net
profit here has increased by 19% and after that news,
after the announcement of the mean results, the
stock took a great jump,
this counter reached almost 706 from the range of 670,
although the close was around 695,
Vibhu ji, how are you looking at this counter,
how do you see its structure in future,
sir, if I talk about ICICI Prudential, then right
now
it is trading at around ₹800 sorry ₹600 ₹81.
But if I
talk about this stock technically, then
technically it does not seem that strong to me right now.  It might be
possible that
its results have been good and this has
already been factored.
In the coming days, I may see
a consolidation zone or
a downward
movement in this stock.  So
it is better that if
you have already made an entry in this stock then this is a
good time to book a profit in it
and if it gives a breakout from here,
that is, above about ₹710, if
this stock stays and is
able to trade there for two to three consecutive days,
then we will see a breakout in it.
But as per its technical
formation, I find it a bit difficult
that it will be able to sustain or even reach there
and
I can see it going somewhere in a consolidation zone.
Some viewers are also joining.  Now let's
start taking questions from the audience.  This
is a question from Sunita Chaudhary ji.  Good afternoon ma'am.
He has taken Prime Focus for ₹27.
It is asking whether
any of these shares can be averaged?  He has mentioned two or three shares.
I will tell you all three of them.
AGI Infra is of 293.  Sider Electric
is priced at Rs 893 and Indraprastha Medical
is priced at Rs 585.  Are any of these three or four stocks
suitable for averaging?
Sir, first of all let us talk about prime focus.
So Prime Focus is currently trading almost at its
all-time high.
This stock is already quite bullish and is showing this to us consistently back to back.
If from here if
this stock gives a breakout, which
means at around ₹250, from here
we see a rise of only ₹7 or ₹8 in this stock
and it gets sustained.  So I
can say to a large extent that
we may see even more upside in this stock.
So it's better to stay in this stock right now.  Do
n't think about exiting this stock.
But don't even think about averaging down
because the stock is trading almost at its all-time high.
Technically it looks quite sound but
still just hold on.  Do
not put further money in it.  The stock looks like it can
give good movement from here.  If I talk
about AGI Infra, then this stock is also
seen to me almost at its all-time high and
this stock has given a good breakout.
After the level of ₹300, we can see a significant rise in this stock as well.
So
it is better that the same thing which
we have noticed in the prime focus, the same thing is
visible to us in this stock also.
So you should definitely hold this stock as well.  Don't be
hasty.  Ah,
we can definitely see very
good levels in both these stocks in the coming times.
If I
talk about Sner Electronics, then
I am seeing a slight down trend in this stock right now
and
they have taken this stock at around ₹893.  Okay and
right now this stock is trading at around ₹00 ₹9.
If you have to think about averaging in this stock, then
I would almost advise you that
if this stock comes at around ₹550
in the coming days, considering the way it is moving in the down trend, then it is
not a big deal.  We
can also see a level of ₹550 within this stock.  So at that time you
can think about making an entry in this stock.  But do
n't even think about making an entry currently
because it is a down trend stock.  Ah, it might be
possible that we
see this stock fall significantly further,
so it's better to let it fall significantly first.
Even at the level of 550, if we
see at that time whether we should make an entry at that time
or wait.  So
you should wait a little bit in this stock right now.  Do
n't even think about making an entry into this stock.  If I
talk about Indraprastha Medical, then
this stock also appears to me to be in a down trend
and there is nothing major going on in this stock as
well.  In the coming days,
if we get to see levels up to ₹350,
right now it is trading around ₹47 from ₹410, then the
levels up to 350 will also be
an important level which will
act as a good support for it and at that
level, if you want to think about making an entry into this stock
or
about averaging, then you can do averaging there.  Do
n't even think about averaging at the current level.
Because if you do averaging in the stocks that are in a down trend, then there are
chances that the stocks may
go down even further from there.  So there you should
keep this stock on hold for a little while now.  The next stock that ma'am has
asked is balurj.  So yes Balu FG
is a good company.  In the recent past,
this stock was beaten quite well
and the current level which I am able to see on its current chart is
around 400 6465,
this is the stock where I can tell you
that yes, if you want to do averaging then you can do
averaging in this stock.
After doing averaging in this stock, I want to tell you one thing
that because this stock has just come from a good down
trend up trend to a straight down trend.  If it
falls significantly downwards, it may take a long time for it to go back up again.
You can see a good amount of consolidation fuzz within this stock.
But yes, around a good
support it
respected the support and is stuck there.  So
if you want to make an entry in this stock above this
or want to do averaging of this stock then you can
definitely do it.
This stock seems to me to be just a sandbag
within which you can do averaging.
Apart from this, two stocks are around their all-time high,
so do not do averaging there also
and two stocks appear to me to be in further down trend,
so do not do averaging there also.
Ok?  The next question we have received is from Sanjeev
Kumar ji.  Look, there is shortage of time so I will be
able to take only one question from each viewer.
He has bought Kitex at ₹275.
Should I average it, hold it or sell it
?  Sir,
I want to tell you one thing about Sir's garment that
due to the trade deal between India and USA, Kitex Garment's stock has suffered a
lot of
loss. The US government
imposed taxes on clothes, so they were going to launch
a complete project in the
USA market within the next one or two years,
but that entire project of
theirs got shelved somewhere,
only and only
because of the trade deal between India and USA, and one of the most
effective companies which has been affected is
Kitex Garment's
company.  The company is very good.   The
management is very sound.
These people are able to achieve good growth year on year in a very good manner.
But
due to all of the sudden relationship between India and USA,
this company is having to
travel temporarily.  If you might be
inside this stock it will
not be a big deal.  In the coming days, we may
also see levels of ₹1 to ₹25 in this stock.
If you
want to do averaging there, then it will be a
better opportunity for you because
this stock has become a consistently down trend.
Aldo is a very good company.
If you
can invest in this stock over a long-term horizon, it
can give you very good returns.  But
in the current scenario, the
situation has changed a bit for this stock.  So you
wait till the level of 125.  There
you should think about averaging it.
You should not think about averaging at the current level.
Ok.   Let's move ahead.  This is
Narendra ji's question.   Is
fresh entry made in adan green
for mid term?  Vibhu ji, the
results of Adani Group shares are about to come.
After January 20, most of the results came
that their dates were around January 22.
How do you like Adani Green?
Sir, if I talk about Adani Green,
Adani stocks had done very
well earlier.  From 2020 to
2022-23, these Adani stocks made a
great splash.  But after that,
somewhere or the other, we are seeing this Adani Group
going into a complete consolidation zone.
And now if I talk about
recently, then for the last one and a half years,
I am not seeing any special movement in this stock.
Adani
Green is also hovering around a good range of ₹700 to ₹900.  There is
no significant movement inside it.
I like Adani Group very much.
Adani Energy is also
one of the leading companies in India and I see that
Adani Green's business is expanding a lot in the coming time.
But I still see this stock
in a consolidation zone.  I do not
think that this stock is going to
break the consolidation range that it is currently in.  Might be possible in the near term.
If you want to plan for a small trade, then
in the coming time, if you get this stock in the range of up to 850, then there can be a
good
opportunity to make an entry in it
but only for short duration and you
can plan your exit near about
1000 or 150, then you
can plan a small trade in it in this way, swing trades.  But until this range is broken,
I do
not see any significant movement in the stock.   So
you just play it for a small range.
Make an entry around 850 and
maintain your stop loss around 850.
We can consider targets around ₹800 or ₹20 and up to ₹1000 in this.   Let's move ahead.  The
next question we have is
from Nikhil Agarwal.  Garuda Construction please
tell on this account.  Bought it for ₹195.
What is medium term view?
Ok.
The way we
see the technical chart of Garura Construction,
it seems positive to me in the medium term.
If you have
made an entry in the stock then definitely
hold it.  Do not plan at all to exit at this level.  If
I talk about important resistance, then
your level of an important resistance increases at around ₹220.
If this stock stays at the level of ₹220 for five to
six days, then definitely
we can see a good rise in it.
I do
n't know Garuda Construction fundamentally well enough to know what its numbers are.
What is its management like?  But
according to the technical charts, I
see this stock as bullish somewhere.  If
entry is already being made in this then there is going to be
an important resistance
level from 220 to 222.  There you
can book your profit.  And then
we can look at the other scripts.
Ok?  The next question we have received is from Rajesh
Kothari ji.  They are asking that the long
term investors are GMR Airport and
Gillette, in which they are making profits of 20 to 30%.
Which one to hold and which one to sell?
Sir, if I talk about Gillette, then Gillette company
itself seems to me to be a very unique company.
The kind of
products they launch and the way they
market it, I somehow like the
company a lot.  But now
this stock has consistently come down from ₹11,000 to
₹8,000.
We are also seeing a lot of beating happening at this counter.
But here I
feel that whatever upside this stock had to come from its ah down trend has already come.
From here onwards, we also see chances of a strong reversal in
this stock.
So you should definitely hold JLet India now
because
this stock was in a down trend for a long time and
now it is again showing us a reversal upside.
So you just hold on and it's
no big deal.  If you hold it for 2 to 3
years, then
in the coming time we may see levels up to 12, 1100, 12,000.
If you
ask me about stop loss from current level then I would definitely like to tell you about a strict stop loss.
You should work on this counter with a strict stop loss around ₹700.
But the company
is very good and the way the company has
performed in the past, there is
consistent demand in the FMCG sector, so
I have no doubt on Jarrett's capability.
If I talk about GMR, then
GMR is also not quite
close to its all-time high,
this stock had made its all-
time high in 2007 and till now it has
not been able to touch its all-time high, but
the way it is showing an upside rally.
This stock has been in full momentum for the last several days.  So it is not a big deal
if this stock gives a breakout from here
which means there are full chances of giving a breakout around ₹19.
So
after that we may see a rise in this stock also.
Technically, if you
ask me, GMR seems more impressive to me.
Standing right next to the breakout.  But if you
ask me about both the companies then
comparison is a bit difficult because
both are companies from different sectors.
Both of them seem quite positive to me at this time.
So if possible,
continue with your position in both.
I feel that both the companies can
give you good profits in the long run.
One more question, can I take entry in Inox Wind for two to three
years
?
Sir, IX Wind, all these
wind energy companies of our solar sector have
performed very well in the past
but for the past some time, they are
moving towards a consistently down trend
and the way
USA has exited from India's solar energy project a week or two ago,
I am seeing some pressure on the companies of all these sectors of solar energy and wind energy, so it is better that
you keep a distance from all these energy, solar energy
and wind energy companies, green
energy companies for some
time because the
way the situation in India and USA is
not good right now,
we are seeing disinvestment happening in these companies as well, all the
foreign
companies are withdrawing their money, in
this way,
this is not a good news from the energy sector companies from within India.
So with Iox Wind,
I would say do
n't
think about entering it for some time now.  Maintain a wait and watch situation for some time.  It might be
possible that we may see this at even better levels.
Then you
think about making an entry.  Leave the
stock for now.
Okay Vibhu ji.  Any recommendations
you think will work well in this market
?
Sir, according to this market, our
recommendation will be Naveen Floran International,
this is a stock.  This shows that
this stock is trading almost at its all-time high.
This stock has already given a breakout.
Currently it is trading at around
₹5990.
Uh I think this stock
still has a significant upside move ahead.
We can expect up to 20% from the current level
that
we may see a further 20% upside rally in this stock.
So
you viewers must
read out this stock once and you
can think about making an entry in it.   I would
like to give a small disclaimer.  Naveen
Florin is the stock we discussed.
We have neither discussed this with our clients
nor do my family or
I have any entry into the stock.
Purely, we have studied this for a few days
and only after that,
today for the first time on the news channel, we are discussing this stock with you.  The
company has been doing quite well
in the past.  Ah and in the coming times
also I see a 20%
upside movement in the stock from here.  Yes,
I would definitely like to give a stop loss with this stock.
You must also maintain a strict stop loss of approximately ₹5400 in this stock.
That could be a good
breakdown level for this.  If
this stock goes below 5400
then we may see further downside in it.
But overall
this stock looks bullish.
Okay, sir, thank you very much sir, it was
nice of you to give your time to join us, thank you so much,
so we could not take questions from the audience, see there was a
time limit, so some questions from the audience will
always be missed, but you stay tuned
with Mani, your questions will be taken, if not today then tomorrow,
and keep watching our live show,
thank you.